(Sheldon:)No, I said you were teaching
someone a lesson. Now let's go.
(Bill:)What are you guys working on?
Oh, we're making nano vacuum tubes.
(Bill:)-That's interesting.
-Haven't you stolen enough from me?
Back off, bow tie!
(Penny:)Hey, guys, what do you think?
(Amy:)Wow, Penny, good job.
Thanks. Target, 4.99.
I'm getting a drink.
(Amy:)-What are you working on?
-I'm making a necklace for my mom.
(Amy:)That's sweet.
(Raj:)Yeah, she and my dad are
going through a bit of a rough patch,
(Raj:)so I wanted to do something to let
her know I was thinking about her.
(Penny:)What's going on with them?
(Raj:)They're just having
a little trouble communicating.
(Raj:)My dad says it's because
the sound of my mom's voice
(Raj:)makes him want to tear his ears off
and sew them over his eyes
(Raj:)so he never has to look at her again.
(Amy:)-Hi.
-Hey, guys.
(Howard:)Look who's here to put
the "Jew" in "Jewelry Night."